condoliving.ph 2014-04-01

# Privacy Policy | CondoLiving.ph - Condo Buying and Searching Made Easier!

**COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY**  
This site is owned and operated by CondoLiving.ph, a property of Sproads Media Inc. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At CondoLiving.ph, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.  
Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

**INFORMATION THAT CONDOLIVING.PH GATHERS AND TRACKS**

CondoLiving.ph gathers two types of information about users:

Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submission to receive our electronic newsletters, create their own personal profile, create and customize their own property pages, post property information, pictures and videos.

CondoLiving.ph gathers information through aggregated tracking, derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our website. This information allows us to better customize our content to readers' needs and help our advertisers and sponsors understand the demographics of our audience better. Because CondoLiving.ph derives its revenue mainly from sponsorships and advertisments, providing such an aggregated demographic data is essential in keeping our services free for users. Under in no circumstances does CondoLiving.ph divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

**CondoLiving.ph Gathers User Information Through The Following Processes:**

**Optional Voluntary Information**

We offer the following free services, all of which require the voluntary submission of personal information by the users:

1\. Electronic newsletters Policy (Dispatches)  
CondoLiving.ph offers a free electronic newsletter to users who voluntarily subscribe by providing their email addresses. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list at any time by following the link to the subscription management page provided in every newsletter. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

2\. Policy on posting property details  
Users who are interested to post property information, images and videos must register separately to avail these services, although they do not need to register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address, and other relevant contact information.

3\. "E-mail this to a friend" and "Social media share" Policy  
Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or document by clicking "e-mail this to a friend" or clicking the social media icons. The user must provide their email address as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

**Privacy Policy Template Changes**

**Children**  
Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without parental consent.

**Usage tracking**  
CondoLiving.ph tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data on individual users. CondoLiving.ph does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string, or information contained in every user's browser.

CondoLiving.ph sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this form of tracking is never associated with individual users. Based on the traffic in those areas, we determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us to continue to build a better service for you.

**Cookies**  
We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information that you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookies created by other sites. CondoLiving.ph uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive a warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.

**Privacy Policy Use**

**USE OF INFORMATION**

CondoLiving.ph uses information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters, post details, images, and customize their channel. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule, and occasionally send out special editions for subscribers who might be particularly interested. CondoLiving.ph never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

We track information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on the traffic. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall, as this helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in the Search function as one of the many ways to determine what interests our users, but don't track which terms a specific individual enters.

CondoLiving.ph creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allow our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Since we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

**SHARING OF THE INFORMATION**

CondoLiving.ph uses the above-described information to customize our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience demographic. This is essential in keeping our service free. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

**SECURITY**

CondoLiving.ph operates secure data networks protected by industry-standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

**OPT-OUT POLICY**

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

Opting not to register and receive our electronic newsletters.  
Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using this site, you consent and allow the collection and use of this information by CondoLiving.ph. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
